# **CONTACT**

Phone: 0860303129

Email:

ciantiernan1997@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ciantiernan/

### **EXPERIENCE**

Aug 2021 - Present

Digigrow

**Full Stack Web Developer** 

Jun 2020 – Jul 2021

Inkerman Technologies

**Junior Web Developer** 

Jan 2018 - May 2018

SightseAR

**Web Developer** 

## **EDUCATION**

2015 - 2019

Dundalk Institute of Technology

Bachelors in Multimedia Web Development

2014 - 2015

Drogheda Institute of Further Education

Fetac Level 5 in IT & Computing

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a 24-year-old Junior Full Stack Developer based in Drogheda, County Louth. I am currently working remotely for Digigrow Consulting on a full-time basis where I use many technologies such as ReactJS, NodeJS and Redux! I work closely with other developers and pride myself in my ability to work as a part of a team and organisational skills.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Below is a list of technical skills I have acquired over the past 5 years I have been coding!

_							
•	ReactJS	•	Ionic	•	Postman	•	SASS
•	NodeJS	•	TailwindCSS	•	Basic AWS Knowledge	•	MySQL
•	ExpressJS	•	Bootstrap	•	Linux	•	REST API's
•	MongoDB	•	Redux	<ul> <li>JavaScript</li> </ul>	JavaScript	•	Git
•	HTML	•	CSS			•	PHP

## **PROJECTS**

Below are some notable projects I have worked on. However, you can see them in more detail with images <a href="here!">here!</a>

#### **Queen Healthcare**

ReactJS, Redux, NodeJS, MongoDB, SASS

A job search and application website that contains file uploads and CRUD functionality. I completed this project in around a month and found my biggest task and biggest accomplishment to be implementing multiple file uploads on a job application form.

#### **Diamond Point Web App**

ReactJS(hooks), Redux, TailwindCSS, NodeJS, MongoDB

A client management app for a security company with the ability to log contact events! Included in this is an excel sheet reader than converts existing data in an xlsx file and imports in into a MongoDB database for future use!

#### **Rapido Booking System**

HTML, CSS, PHP, MySQL, Ajax, Bootstrap

A restaurant booking platform used by various businesses where restaurants can log bookings in advanced, manage them easily, view them via a planner and quickly add walk in bookings!